Melich, Tanya M.; Papers apap079
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- CBS, Inc., 1961-2009; Undated; 4; 3.4 Cubic Feet
  - CBS—Public Issues Proposals, 1980 (Box 2 (4-CBS, Inc.), Folder 11)
  - Employee Appointments and General Announcements, 1980-1981; Undated (Box 2 (4-CBS, Inc.), Folder 12)
  - Information about Thomas H. Wyman (President CBS. Inc), 1980-1981 (Box 3 (4-CBS, Inc.), Folder 1)
  - State of CBS (Clippings), 1986 (Box 3 (4-CBS, Inc.), Folder 2)
- The Ripon Society, 1961-1998; Undated; 5; 3.2 cubic ft.
  The Ripon Society is a Republican Party research and policy organization of which Tanya Melich was a member. It formed in 1964 with the aim of improving the Republican Party, as members believed their original values had been compromised by catering to an extreme right-wing contingency. This series contains many copies of The Ripon Forum, a newsletter regarding politics which reflected the Society's views. The The Ripon Forum was published each month, and occasionally the Society issued a small, supplemental version, usually on the 1st or 15th of the month. There are also several copies of the Ripon Quarterly, a magazine publication of the organization. Both The Ripon Forum and Ripon Quarterly y are missing issues in the series, so not all dates are inclusive.
  The series also contains Daily Office Files which include correspondence, press releases, news clippings, and reports by Melich. The year 1973 has the most substantial amount of material with a number of items related to Watergate, Nixon, and his eventual impeachment. There is also information on the New Leadership Fund, which was a fund-raising committee designed to help Republican candidates through monetary donations or research and campaign assistance. The materials include correspondence and reports related to the committee.
  The series includes a few folders related to the Ripon Society chapter in New York City. These materials include correspondence, local government newsletters, and articles. The "Lessons of Victory" material contains chapter outlines and multiple drafts of chapter 3, "The Failures of the Republican Moderates" by Melich. It discusses the Nixon campaign, weaknesses within the Republican Party, and the political transition to the future. George H.W. Bush, then chair of the Republican National Committee, convened the Rule 29 committee in 1973. The purpose of the committee was to review, study, and work with the states and territories regarding the rules adopted by the 1972 Republican National Convention. It was also supposed to benefit the relationship between the Republican National Committee, Republican State Committees, and other Republican organizations. Items include memorandums, news clippings, and reports between the Rule 29 Committee and the Women's Political Caucus. It also includes Melich's testimony before the Rule 29 Committee in 1974.
  The Ripon Society filed two lawsuits against the Republican National Committee and Republican Party, the first from 1970 to 1973 and the second from 1974 to 1975. The Society believed the Committee's process of allocating delegates was unconstitutional. Items for both suits are filed in two sections: general papers and legal papers. The general papers include memorandums, correspondence, press releases, news clippings, and reports. The legal papers include legal documents such as complaints and briefs. The law firm Patterson, Belknap and Webb in New York City handled the Ripon Society's case.
  The book The New Political Order: A History of the Conservative Infrastructure is by John S. Saloma (1934-1983). The files about the book include notes, correspondence, and a review by Melich from 1984. Saloma was a founding member of the Ripon Society and President of the Ripon Society from 1963 to 1967. The manuscript was published posthumously under the title, Ominous Politics: The New Conservative Labyrinth (New York: Hill and Wang, 1984.)
  - "Advance", 1961-1963 (Box 1 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 1)
  - "Advance", 1963 (Box 1 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 2)
  - Daily Office Files, 1965-1966; Undated (Box 1 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 3-21)
  - "The Lessons of Victory" Chapter Outline, 1968 (Box 1 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 22)
  - "The Lessons of Victory" Drafts, 1968 (Box 1 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 23-24)
  - Lawsuit 1970-1973—General Papers, 1970-1972; Undated (Box 1 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 25-28)
  - Lawsuit 1970-1973—Legal Papers, 1971 September-1972 August (Box 1 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 29-39)
  - Lawsuit 1974-1975—General Papers, 1974 January (Box 1 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 40-44)
  - Lawsuit 1974-1975—Legal Papers, 1975 March (Box 1 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 45-51)
  - New Leadership Fund, 1976-1977 (Box 1 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 52-57)
  - New Leadership Fund, 1977-1979 (Box 2 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 1-7)
  - The New Political Order: A History of the Conservative Infrastructure, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 8-9)
  - The New Political Order: A History of the Conservative Infrastructure, manuscript, 1983 (Box 2 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 10-13)
  - Political Committee, 1968-1970 (Box 2 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 14-15)
  - Ripon, 1971-1973 (Box 2 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 16-17)
  - Ripon Administration, 1972-1975; Undated (Box 2 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 18-19)
  - Ripon Conference, May 1976, 1975-1976; Undated (Box 2 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 20)
  - Ripon Forum—A Ripon Research Proposal "Secrecy and National Security: A Program for Congressional Action and Presidential Restraint", 1973 November (Box 2 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 21)
  - The Ripon Forum, Volume I, II, 1965-1966 (Box 2 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 22)
  - The Ripon Forum, Volume III, No. 1-12, 1967 (Box 2 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 23)
  - The Ripon Forum, Volume IV, No. 1-7, 1968 (Box 2 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 24)
  - The Ripon Forum, Volume IV, No. 8-12, 1968 (Box 2 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 25)
  - The Ripon Forum, Volume V, No. 1-6, 1969 (Box 2 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 26)
  - The Ripon Forum, Volume V, No. 7-11, 1969 (Box 2 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 27)
  - The Ripon Forum, Volume VI, No. 1-6, 1970 (Box 2 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 28)
  - The Ripon Forum, Volume VI, No. 7-12, 1970 (Box 2 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 29)
  - The Ripon Forum, Volume VII, No. 1-6, 1971 (Box 2 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 30)
  - The Ripon Forum, Volume VII, No. 9-15, 1971 (Box 2 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 31)
  - The Ripon Forum, Volume VIII, No. 2-13, 1972 (Box 2 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 32)
  - The Ripon Forum, Volume VIII, No. 16-23, 1972 (Box 2 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 33)
  - The Ripon Forum, Volume IX, No. 1-11, 1973 (Box 3 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 1)
  - The Ripon Forum, Volume IX, No. 14-23, 1973 (Box 3 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 2)
  - The Ripon Forum, Volume X, No. 1-20, 1974 (Box 3 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 3)
  - The Ripon Forum, Volume XI, XII, 1975-1976 (Box 3 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 4)
  - The Ripon Forum, Volume XIII, XIV, 1977-1978 (Box 3 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 5)
  - The Ripon Forum, Volume XV, XVI, 1979-1980 (Box 3 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 6)
  - The Ripon Forum, Volume XVIII, XX, XXI, XXIII, 1982; 1984-1985; 1987 (Box 3 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 7)
  - The Ripon Forum, Volume XXIV, XXV, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 8)
  - The Ripon Forum, Volume XXVI, XXVII, 1990-1991 (Box 3 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 9)
  - The Ripon Forum, XXVIII, XXIX, XXXII, XXXIII, 1992-1993; 1997-1998 (Box 3 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 10)
  - Ripon—Gypsy Moths, 1987-1994 (Box 3 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 11)
  - Ripon—"Jaws of Victory", 1972; 1974 (Box 3 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 12)
  - Ripon Meeting, 1976 February 27-1976 February 29 (Box 3 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 13)
  - Ripon National, 1974-1980; Undated (Box 3 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 14-15)
  - Ripon Society—Ripon of NY, 1974 (Box 3 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 16)
  - Ripon New York, 1976-1979 (Box 3 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 17)
  - Ripon New York Conference, 1974-1975; Undated (Box 3 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 18)
  - Ripon of NY, 1975 (Box 3 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 19)
  - Ripon Publications, 1973-1974; Undated (Box 3 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 20-21)
  - Ripon Quarterly, Volume 1, No. 1, 1974 (Box 3 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 22)
  - Ripon Quarterly, Summer 1975 (Volume 2, No. 1) & "GOP Forum", 1976 August 16-1976 August 19 (Box 3 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 23)
  - Ripon Quarterly, Volume. 34, No. 2, 1999 (Box 3 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 24)
  - Ripon Research Consortium Briefing Day, 1974 (Box 3 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 25)
  - Ripon Society, 1973-1985 (Box 3 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 26-27)
  - Ripon Society General Organization Membership, 1975 (Box 3 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 28)
  - Rule 29 Committee, 1975 April-1975 July (Box 3 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 29-33)
  - Watergate-Newspaper Clippings, 1973 (Box 3 (5-The Ripon Society), Folder 34-35)
- New York City Partnership, 1981-1982; Undated; 6; 0.4 cubic ft.
  The New York City Partnership (NYCP) was founded in 1979. David Rockefeller was one of the founders and served as chair during the period covered by these records, Arthur R. Taylor served as president. NYCP began as a collaborative association of 100 businesses, private-sector groups, and civic leaders to assist the city develop innovative volunteer projects. Partners included the Chamber of Commerce and Economic Development Council. The majority of materials in this series concern transit problems in New York City in 1981, a summer job program for high school students, and a lunch hosted by NYCP in 1982 with President Ronald Reagan as a guest.
  - Background Materials—White House, 1981 (Box 1 (6-New York City Partnership), Folder 1)
  - "Material sent to the White House about the New York City partnership", 1981 (Box 1 (6-New York City Partnership), Folder 2-3)
  - New York City Partnership, Inc. News, 1981; Undated (Box 1 (6-New York City Partnership), Folder 4)
  - Overview and Report, 1981 (Box 1 (6-New York City Partnership), Folder 5)
  - Partners—Economic Development Council of New York Inc., Undated (Box 1 (6-New York City Partnership), Folder 6)
  - Summer Jobs for Youth Project Evaluation, 1981 (Box 1 (6-New York City Partnership), Folder 7)
  - Transit—News Clippings, 1981 (Box 1 (6-New York City Partnership), Folder 8)
  - Reagan Lunch, 1982—General Plans (Box 1 (6-New York City Partnership), Folder 9)
  - Reagan Lunch, 1982—Guest List (Box 1 (6-New York City Partnership), Folder 10)
  - Reagan Lunch, 1982—Jim Rosebuch (White House Liaison) (Box 1 (6-New York City Partnership), Folder 11)
  - Reagan Lunch, 1982—Operations (Box 1 (6-New York City Partnership), Folder 12)
  - Reagan Lunch, 1982—Planning Committee Meetings (Box 1 (6-New York City Partnership), Folder 13)
  - Regan Lunch, 1982—Press and Publicity (Box 1 (6-New York City Partnership), Folder 14)
  - Reagan Lunch, 1982—Program (Box 1 (6-New York City Partnership), Folder 15)
  - Reagan Lunch, 1982—Site Visits (Box 1 (6-New York City Partnership), Folder 16)
  - Reagan Lunch, 1982—Student Attendees (Box 1 (6-New York City Partnership), Folder 17)
- United States Commission on Civil Rights New York State Advisory Board, 1967-1984; 7; 1.2 cubic ft.
  Tanya Melich served on the United States Commission on Civil Rights New York State Advisory Board beginning in 1972. Included are folders concerning the Asian American hearings in July 1974. These hearings encompassed issues with employment, immigration, education, health care, images and stereotypes, and housing within the Asian American community. She also served on the subcommittee for sex discrimination. There are also materials relating to affirmative action, racism, and economic status.
  - Reports—"A Time to Listen…A time to Act," "For all the People…By all the people", 1967-1969 (Box 1 (7-United States Commission on Civil Rights New York ), Folder 1)
  - New York State Advisory Committee Information, 1972-1974 (Box 1 (7-United States Commission on Civil Rights New York ), Folder 2)
  - New York State Advisory Committee Report—"The Puerto Rican and Public Employment in New York State", 1973 (Box 1 (7-United States Commission on Civil Rights New York ), Folder 3)
  - News Items, 1973-1981 (Box 1 (7-United States Commission on Civil Rights New York ), Folder 4)
  - "Civil Rights Digest," "Puerto Ricans in the Promised Land" & "Job Discrimination and Affirmative Action", 1974-1975 (Box 1 (7-United States Commission on Civil Rights New York ), Folder 5)
  - New York State Advisory Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (7-United States Commission on Civil Rights New York ), Folder 6)
  - New York State Advisory Committee—Asian American Hearings, 1974 (Box 1 (7-United States Commission on Civil Rights New York ), Folder 7-9)
  - New York State Advisory Committee—Reports, 1974-1977 (Box 1 (7-United States Commission on Civil Rights New York ), Folder 10)
  - New York State Advisory Committee—Sex Discrimination Subcommittee, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (7-United States Commission on Civil Rights New York ), Folder 11)
  - Report—"Desegregating the Boston Public Schools: A Crisis in Civic Responsibility", 1974 (Box 1 (7-United States Commission on Civil Rights New York ), Folder 12)
  - Reports—"The Navajo Nation: An American Colony", 1975 (Box 1 (7-United States Commission on Civil Rights New York ), Folder 13)
  - Report—"Twenty Years After Brown: Equality of Economic Opportunity" (part 3-4), 1975 (Box 1 (7-United States Commission on Civil Rights New York ), Folder 14-15)
  - Report—"Fulfilling the letter and spirit of the law", 1975 (Box 1 (7-United States Commission on Civil Rights New York ), Folder 16)
  - Report—"Statement on Metropolitan School Desegregation", 1977 (Box 1 (7-United States Commission on Civil Rights New York ), Folder 17)
  - Commission on Civil Rights—"Recent Developments, New Opportunities in Civil Rights and Women's Rights", 1977 (Box 1 (7-United States Commission on Civil Rights New York ), Folder 18)
  - Report—"Sex Bias in the U.S. Code", 1977 (Box 1 (7-United States Commission on Civil Rights New York ), Folder 19)
  - "Civil Rights Digest," "National Women's Conference," Vol 10. No. 2, 1978 (Box 1 (7-United States Commission on Civil Rights New York ), Folder 20)
  - Reports—"Statement on Affirmative Action," "Affirmative Action in the 1980s…", 1977; 1981 (Box 1 (7-United States Commission on Civil Rights New York ), Folder 21)
  - Report—"Toward an Understanding of Bakke", 1979 (Box 1 (7-United States Commission on Civil Rights New York ), Folder 22)
  - Report—"More Hurdles to Clear: Women and Girls in Competitive Athletics", 1980 (Box 1 (7-United States Commission on Civil Rights New York ), Folder 23)
  - Report—"The Tarnished Golden Door: Civil Rights Issues in Immigration", 1980 (Box 1 (7-United States Commission on Civil Rights New York ), Folder 24)
  - United States Commission on Civil Rights—Conference, 1981 (Box 1 (7-United States Commission on Civil Rights New York ), Folder 25)
  - Report—"Civil Rights: A National, Not a Special Interest", 1981 (Box 1 (7-United States Commission on Civil Rights New York ), Folder 26)
  - Report—"Consultations on the Affirmative Action Statement of the U.S. Commission on Civil Rights" (vol. 1-2), 1981 (Box 1 (7-United States Commission on Civil Rights New York ), Folder 27-28)
  - "Perspectives," U.S. Commission on Civil Rights, 1982 (Box 1 (7-United States Commission on Civil Rights New York ), Folder 29)
  - Report—"Comparable Worth: Issues for the 80s" (Vol. 1), 1984 (Box 1 (7-United States Commission on Civil Rights New York ), Folder 30)
  - Report—"Comparable Worth: Issues for the 80s" (Vol. 2), 1984 (Box 2 (7-United States Commission on Civil Rights New York ), Folder 1)
- International Women's Year, 1976-1978; Undated; 8; 0.8 cubic ft.
  In November of 1977 the National Women's Conference was held in Houston, Texas. This meeting was preceded by state-wide meetings to elect delegates to attend the National Conference. At the state meetings and the National Conference the following issues were discussed: abortion, equal pay, the Equal Rights Amendment (ERA), child care, divorce and marriage laws, laws regarding rape and domestic violence, and other issues. The series includes materials related to the New York State and Utah Women's Meetings and the National Conference. This material includes pre-conference newsletters, reports, correspondence, agendas, conference materials, notes, and news clippings. Tanya Melich was co-chair of the New York State IWY Resolutions Committee in the summer of 1977. She was one of the few Republicans on the committee.
  - Business Council for the United Nations Decade for Women, Undated (Box 1 (8-International Women's Year), Folder 1)
  - Manual Revisions National Commission on the Observance of International Women's Year, 1977 March 17 (Box 1 (8-International Women's Year), Folder 2)
  - National Advisory Committee, 1977 June-1978 June (Box 1 (8-International Women's Year), Folder 3)
  - National Commission on the Observance of International Women's Year— Report, 1976 (Box 1 (8-International Women's Year), Folder 4)
  - National Women's Conference—News Clippings, 1977 April-1978 March (Box 1 (8-International Women's Year), Folder 5)
  - National Women's Conference News—October-December, 1977 October-1977 December (Box 1 (8-International Women's Year), Folder 6)
  - National Women's Conference Texas, 1977 July-1977 December (Box 1 (8-International Women's Year), Folder 7-10)
  - State Women's Meeting New York, 1977; Undated (Box 1 (8-International Women's Year), Folder 11-14)
  - State Women's Meeting New York—May-June, 1977 May-1977 June (Box 2 (8-International Women's Year), Folder 1)
  - State Women's Meeting New York—July, 1977 July (Box 2 (8-International Women's Year), Folder 2-6)
  - State Women's Meeting New York—News clippings, July-November, 1977 July-1977 November (Box 2 (8-International Women's Year), Folder 7)
  - State Women's Meeting New York—September, 1977 September (Box 2 (8-International Women's Year), Folder 8)
  - State Women's Meeting Utah, Undated (Box 2 (8-International Women's Year), Folder 9)
  - State Women's Meeting Utah, Undated (Box 2 (8-International Women's Year), Folder 10)
  - State Women's Meeting Utah—News Clippings, Jan-December, 1977 January-1977 December (Box 2 (8-International Women's Year), Folder 11)
- Organizations, 1958-2016; Undated; 9; 10.6 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically
  Tanya Melich consistently received material from numerous political, academic, and social organizations. Many of the folders contain content such as letters, brochures, newsletters, or publications. Melich was involved in some of the organizations represented, such as the National Women's Education Fund (NWEF), for which she served as President from 1980-1983. There is extensive information relating to NWEF operations such as budget information, fundraising efforts, board information, and publications. There is also documentation from the Women's Political Caucus, a grassroots organization dedicated to increasing women's involvement in politics, which has historically been male-dominated. Melich also collected information on the Planned Parenthood Federation of America, including yearly reports, informational publications for communities, and the tactics it took to combat STOPP, an anti-Planned Parenthood group. Melich was also very active as a board member with her local chapter, Planned Parenthood of New York City, so many records related to that chapter are administrative in nature.
  In general, many of the organizations relate particularly to women's causes and the Republican Party. However, there is also organizational information on groups dedicated to combating environmental issues (especially overpopulation). There is a relatively large amount of information on The International Women's Rights Action Watch including correspondence, documents regarding the Convention on the Elimination of the Discrimination Against Women (CEDAW), and a 12 year run of its newsletter The Woman's Watch. The folders are arranged in alphabetical order by the full name of the organization.
  There are some audio/video items in this series as well, including cassette tapes from an anti-Planned Parenthood group. Planned Parenthood was able to secure the tapes and used them to study the arguments of the opposing groups so it could better respond in the media.
  - The 80% Majority Campaign—"The Campaign Report," Vol. 3 No. 14-23, Vol. 4 1-10, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 1)
  - The 80% Majority Campaign—"The Campaign Report," Vol. 4 No. 11-17, Vol. 5 No. 1, 2, 1991; 1993 (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 2)
  - 85 Broads, 2003; Undated (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 3)
  - The Academy of Political Science—"Urban Riots: Violence and Social Change, Proceedings of the Academy of Political Science", 1968 (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 4)
  - Alan Guttmacher Institute, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 5)
  - Alan Guttmacher Institute, "Sex and America's Teenagers", 1994 (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 6)
  - American Association of Political Consultants—"Politea," and Misc. Information, 1997; Undated (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 7)
  - American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees—"Why isn't the economy working for workers?", Undated (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 8)
  - Arts and Business Council, Inc., 1991 (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 9)
  - Asian Americans for Fair Media—"The Asian Image in the U.S.", Undated (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 10)
  - Association for Public Policy Analysis and Management— Memorandums, 1981 (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 11)
  - Association for Women Journalists, 1994 (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 12)
  - Bass & Howes, Inc., 1993-1994; Undated (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 13)
  - Business Leaders Sensible Priorities—"Sensible Budget Priorities for America's Children", 2001 (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 14)
  - Campaign for Justice for Home Care Workers, 1991 (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 15)
  - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace—"The Future of the Strategic Arms Race: Options for the 1970s", 1969 (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 16)
  - Catholics for a Free Choice "Mujeres e Iglesia Sexualidad y Aborto en America Latina", 1989 (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 17)
  - Catholics for a Free Choice "Mujeres e Iglesia Sexualidad y Aborto en America Latina", 1998 (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 18)
  - Celebrate Life Committee, 1973 (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 19)
  - Center for Advanced Study of International Development—"New Challenges New Opportunities", 1988 (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 20)
  - Center for the American Woman and Politics, 1974-1976 (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 21)
  - Center for the American Woman and Politics—Conference for Leaders of Organizations of Women Public Officials, 1980 (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 22)
  - Center for the American Woman and Politics—"Fact Sheets", 1990-1995; Undated (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 23-24)
  - Center for the American Woman and Politics—"Fact Sheets" and General Information, 1993-1994; Undated (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 25)
  - Center for the American Woman and Politics (CAWP)—General Information, 1986-1990; Undated (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 26)
  - Center for the American Woman and Politics—Legislative Conference, 1989 November 16-1989 November 19 (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 27)
  - Center for the American Woman and Politics—News and Notes, 1991-1993; Undated (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 28)